

# PAMELA LOBOGUERRERO GARCÍA

Phone: 312 429 2925

City: Bogotá - Colombia

Follow my work:



/pamela-loboguerrero



/pameloga



'paloga87

## WHO I AM?

I am a Front-End Developer and Professional in Marketing and Advertising. I am a graduede of the Politecnico Grancolombiano, a four year University in Bogotá, Colombia, I have 5 years experience as a Porject Manager, Web Designer and Developer and Account Executive. I have a broad command of the English language; I am a disciplined, responsible, organized and enterprising person, with a high capacity for learning and adaptability. I develop my work objectively, efficiently and honestly.

# **EDUCATION**

Course

WEB DEVELOPMENT - FULL STACK Acamica (2018)

Certified

CONVERGENT CONTENTS AND DIGITAL ADVERTISING Ministerio de las TIC (2016)

Certified

TRAINING IN CONSULTANCY FU Politecnico Grancolombiano (2014)

Career

PROFESSIONAL MARKETING AND ADVERTISING FU Politecnico Grancolombiano (2008 - 2013)

Course

ILUSTRATOR and PHOTOSHOP CompuClub (2011)

Course

English (basic, medium, advanced) London Empire Academy (2007)

# **ABILITIES**

# HTML5 CSS JavaScript PHP Wordpress Git Angular Illustrator PhotoShop

Follow my work:





git /paloga87

### **EXPERIENCE**

PUBLICITV Proyect Manager

Date: Febrero de 2019 – Actualmente

Phone: +57 (1) 317 7917 Address: Calle 73 # 7 – 50

Tasks: Management of web projects, diagnosis of effectiveness and functionality of sites, analysis of consumer behavior, development and layout of custom web pages and maintenance of websites on free platforms.

Cuentas: Café 18, Rebel Guide, El trasto, Droguerías Galénica.

# MULLEN LOWE PROFERO Web Integrator

Date: Marzo de 2017 a Mayo de 2018

Phone: +57 (1) 605 8000 Address: Carrera 9 # 79a 19

Tasks: Development and layout of customized websites and

maintenance of websites on free platforms

Cuentas: Arturo Calle, Etb, Loteria de Bogotá, Mercedez Benz, A

Comer Huevo, Aruba.

#### RACO AGENCIA

Project Management and Front-end Developer

Date: Julio de 2014 a Marzo de 2017 / Mayo de 2018 a Enero 2019

Phone: +57 (311) 451 5778 Address: Carrera 47a # 118 - 08

Tasks: Management of web projects, design, development and maintenance of web pages on free platforms, customer and portfolio management

Cuentas: Ventas en Linea, Triple k, Mental performance, T&M Urbanismo, Editorial Buena Semilla, Equipos Urrego, Vimafer.